（医療忍者たち）おっ
Who're they?
誰だ？
Oh, that's...
（医療忍者）あっ あの方々は…
チヨバア様にエビゾウじい様だ
Grandmother Chiyo...
and Grandfather Ebizo.
No way. I thought they were supposed
to have long since been retired.
まさか とうに引退されたはずでは…
"Treatment Room 3"
Oh, we have been expecting you.
（バキ）おおっ
お待ちしておりました
Please enter.
さあ どうぞ 中へ
I think you all know who
these people are.
みんな 知ってると思うが
チヨ様にエビゾウ様だ
This is Chiyo-sama and Ebizo-sama.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
（医療忍者たち）はっ
（カンクロウ）うっ ううう…
（エビゾウ）うん？
Hm? If I'm not mistaken, this is...
こやつは 確か…
It's Kankuro.
（バキ）カンクロウです
The current Kazekage-sama's older brother.
今の風影かぜかげ様の兄の…
Oh, that's right.
おお そうじゃったな
（チヨ）う～ん
You checked his blood, right?
（チヨ）血液は見たんじゃろ？
あっ はい これを
Y-Yes. Please look at this.
うん… この組成そせい
I've never seen...
composition like this before.
初めて見るな
はい おそらく新種の毒かと
Yes. We believe it might be
a new type of poison.
Have you tried an antidote?
（チヨ）解毒薬は試したのか？
For the time being,
we tried using what we had.
手に入るものは一応
But none had any identifiable effects.
効果が確認できたものは
ありませんが
I see...
そうか
Ordinarily, he would just finish the job...
いつでも とどめを刺そうと
思えば刺せたはずじゃが
It appears he's very confident
about his poison.
よほど 己の毒に
自信があるとみえる
Leaving his prey as is
on purpose is just like Sasori.
あえて放置したか
いかにもサソリらしいわい
（デイダラ）
やっと 砂ともおさらばだな うん
Finally we're out of the Sand.
I hate making people wait...
Let's hurry.
（サソリ）人を待たせるのは嫌いだ
急ぐぞ
（デイダラ）やれやれ
Good grief. Whose fault was it
that it took this long?
誰のせいで こんなに
時間 食ったと思ってんだ
（サソリ）それは お互いさまだ
That goes for both of us.
Oh yeah.
（デイダラ）そうだった うん
♪～
A voice heard in the distance gives me a hint.
tooku de kikoeru koe wo hinto ni
One by one like-minded people are standing up.
hitori mata hitori tachiagaru doushi
Lets overturn all the everyday, monotonous things.
kurikaesu dake no fudan doori kutsugaesu
I'm ready, are you ready?
junbi iize are you ready
A shiver spreads through my body, violently ringing stomping.
karadajuu furuwasu shindou ni hageshiku uchinarase yo stomping
Constantly stirring in me, it calls me.
taezu tsuki ugokasu call me
Catching that unchanging, never wavering story, Come on!
kawarazu yuru ga nutsukamu story come on
Everybody stand up! Today's the best time to get up!
everybody stand up agero kyou ichiban no jikan da
Before my eyes you still don't stop, speed hunter.
me ni mo tomaranu speed hunter
Everyone is a victim to that attraction, Yeah! (Come on!)
daremo ga mina toriko kanban yeah come on
Everybody Hands up! It's the highly anticipated Hero's Come Back!
everybody hands up matashita na hero's come back
Hold up your fingers and count down.
zujou kazoe yubi oru count down
Let's go, 3-2-1 make some noise!
ikuze 3-2-1 make some noise
Are you ready for a few risks?
hey yo whoa tashou no risuku wa kakugo desho
You have to get up no matter how many times you fall. (Get it on!)
nanka korundatte tatsu get it on
It's not some conspiracy, just a paper-thin session
nare ai ja nai ze kami hitoe no sesshon
The pent up feelings turn into a crystal.
irikunda kanjou kidzukiageta kesshou
The rising cheers will become your courage.
wakiagaru kansei ga yuuki tonaru
So stand up now, no matter how much pain you feel.
tachiagareba ima ijou kurushimi tomonau
But in the end I'm sure you'll laugh.
soredemo saigo wa kitto warau
Everything will be swept away in victory and cheer.
subete sarau shouri to kansei
Everybody stand up! Today's the best time to get up!
everybody stand up agero kyou ichiban no jikan da
Before my eyes you still don't stop, speed hunter.
me ni mo tomaranu speed hunter
Everyone is a victim to that attraction, Yeah! (Come on!)
daremo ga mina toriko kanban yeah come on
Everybody Hands up! It's the highly anticipated Hero's Come Back!
everybody hands up matashita na hero's come back
～♪
Hold up your fingers and count down.
zujou kazoe yubi oru count down
Let's go, 3-2-1 make some noise!
ikuze 3-2-1 make some noise
Sealing Jutsu - Nine Phantom Dragons
All right.
よし
ああっ！
ふん…
This one didn't work, either.
これでもダメか
You haven't tried anything else?
ほかには 何も
手を打っておらんのか？
For the time being,
一応 木ノ葉このはへは
we have requested the Leaf for
a specialist team to be dispatched.
スペシャリストチームの派遣を
要請しております
It would be best to wait for their arrival.
彼らの到着を待つのがいちばんです
ふん なんと他人任せな
Talk about depending on others.
This happened because you depend
on alliances with other lands
お前らが他国との同盟に甘え
and conduct nothing
but slipshod education.
ズサンな教育しかしなかったから
こうなるんじゃ
なっ… 甘えるなど
It is not... our intention to
depend on others.
決してそのようなつもりは…
しかたなかろうよ
I guess it can't be helped...
It's his fault for losing his cool
and pursuing too far.
冷静さを欠いて 深追いした
こいつが悪いのよ
忍ともあろうものが
A Shinobi is the last person
who should do that.
うっ う…
（医療忍者たち）ああ…
What's the point of trusting
and being totally dependent
（チヨ）木ノ葉などを信用し
頼り切ってどうする？
on the likes of the Leaf?
Improving the strength of your own village
should be your top priority.
おのが里の能力の向上を
第一とせんからだ
人は人 我は我じゃ
They are them, we are us.
Listen. An amicable alliance is nothing
but a pipe dream.
よいか 友好同盟など
しょせん 絵そらごとじゃ
At times like this,
the most we can expect
こんなときは 形式上
役立たずの下っ端が
遣わされてくるのが関の山じゃ
is for them to send us some
useless underlings for form's sake.
That would never happen...
まさか そんなことは
That's how it goes.
（チヨ）そういうもんじゃ
Everyone looks out for themselves.
皆 自分がかわいいからの
Okay, break's over.
（はたけカカシ）よし 休憩終わり
Huh? Kakashi-sensei, where's Naruto?
（春野はるのサクラ）あれ？
カカシ先生 ナルトは？
Up there.
あそこ
えっ
（うずまきナルト）砂まで あと１日
One more day until
we get to the Sand.
We have to hurry.
急ぐってばよ
Okay, let's get going.
（カカシ）さあ 出発だ
ハァ ハァ
うっ うう…
This is not good.
（チヨ）もう いかん
Poisons are my specialty,
but even I can't figure this out.
毒は専門じゃが
こりゃ わしにも分からん
Even you, Chiyo-sama...?
（バキ）チヨ様でも？
At best, he has one day...
（チヨ）もって あと１日
（エビゾウ）あすの夜明けが
迎えられるかどうかといったところか
He may not even make it
to dawn tomorrow, I'd say.
That Sasori has sure grown considerably.
まったく サソリのヤツ
ずいぶんと成長したもんじゃ
What in the world should we do?
一体 どうすれば…
Well, the only one who might
know more about antidotes than me
まあ わしより
解毒に詳しいというと
would be the
Leaf's slug princess, Tsunade.
木ノ葉の
ナメクジ綱手つなで姫ぐらいじゃ
I had a lot of trouble with her
during the great war.
対戦中 わしの合成した毒を
ことごとく かい毒し
She would decipher all the poisons
I created and concoct antidotes.
解毒薬を調合されて手を焼いた
その木ノ葉とも 今は同盟国
And now we're allies with the Leaf.
All we can do is send for her and
have her look at Kankuro.
すぐにでも呼びつけて
診てもらうしかあるまいの
しかし その方も今や ほかより
But she is now the Hokage
and would not be able to
leave her village so easily.
簡単に里を
離れるわけにはいかないでしょう
それに たとえ
来てくれる運びになったとしても
And even if she were to come,
it takes three days to get here
from the Leaf.
木ノ葉から砂までは
３日かかります
I know. Nobody's seriously thinking
of summoning her.
分かっとる
誰も本気で あやつを
呼びつけようとは思っとらん
I don't like that slug girl, anyway.
大体 わしゃ
あのナメクジ娘が好かん
（綱手）あ～ ああ…
（シズネ）
大丈夫ですか？ 綱手様
Are you okay, Tsunade-sama?
Yeah.
（綱手）ああっ
There's a cold going around,
so please take care.
（シズネ）
最近 かぜ はやってますから
気をつけてくださいね
Thanks.
すまん
It's been two days
since Team Kakashi left.
（綱手）カカシ班が出発して２日
They should be arriving
tomorrow morning.
予定なら
あすの朝には着くはずだが…
（綱手）ん？
This is a bad sign.
不吉な…
Don't tell me...!
まさか
Group 3, 17037... I knew it.
３組の117037
やっぱりか
見事に当たってる
I won. And first prize at that.
しかも １等賞
This is really a bad omen.
これは相当 縁起が悪いな
Shizune. Are you there, Shizune?
シズネ！ シズネはいるか
（ナルト）ハア… やった
All right!
It's the desert!
砂漠だ
The Village Hidden in the Sand
is up ahead.
（テマリ）
この向こうに砂隠すながくれの里がある
I'll take the lead from here.
（テマリ）ここからは私が先導する
We're counting on you.
（カカシ）頼む
We're here.
着いたな うん
Let's go.
（サソリ）行くぞ
You're late. Prepare immediately.
（暁リーダー）遅かったな
すぐ準備しろ
The Jinchuriki was unexpectedly strong.
（デイダラ）思いのほか強くってな
人柱力じんちゅうりきってのは
（暁リーダー）はあっ！
All right, gather.
よし 集合しろ
Now, let us begin.
さて 始めるか
（砂すなの里さとの忍）
通路のトラップと 岩の撤去作業は
まもなく完了します
We will soon be done removing the traps
and rocks from the road.
（バキ）ご苦労
Good work.
現在 遺体の収容作業を
行っておりますが
We are currently working on
gathering the bodies.
気になることが１つ
But there is one thing that is
a matter of concern.
（バキ）なんだ？
What is it?
由良ゆうら隊長が見当たらないのです
We have not yet found Captain Yuura.
What?
（バキ）何？
隊長が 事件の前に
通路に向かったのは
It is clear that the Captain was
heading for the road
はっきりしてるのですが…
before the incident.
死体はおろか
服の切れ端すら見つからないのです
We have not even found
a scrap of his clothing,
let alone his body.
それは妙だな
That's strange.
敵の目をかいくぐって
風影様を追跡しているか
He's either slipped past the enemy
and is in pursuit,
or perhaps nobody noticed
that he was killed.
あるいは 人知れず殺されたか…
まだ生きてるのであれば
応援を送ってやりたいが
I'd like to send backup for him
if he's still alive.
But if we don't know where he is...
所在がつかめぬのでは…
（シズネ）
お呼びになりましたか？ 綱手様
Did you call me, Tsunade-sama?
ああ
Yes...
砂隠れの里に増援部隊を送る
I want to send reinforcements to
the Village Hidden in the Sand.
（シズネ）増援ですか
Reinforcements?
そろそろ あいつらが
前の任務を終えて戻ってくるはずだ
They should be about done
with their previous mission
and on their way back by now.
あいつら…
Them?
あっ はい すぐに手配します
Oh. Yes, ma'am. I'll make
the preparations immediately.
最悪の事態も考えられるか
Can the worst-case scenario
be considered?
（暁リーダー）
これから ３日３晩はかかる
From now, it will take three days
and three nights.
Keep your attention to
your real body as well.
皆 本体のほうにも
気を配っておくよう
それから ゼツ
And Zetsu, you keep watch on the outside
with the body for the time being.
本体で一応 外の見張りをしろ
いちばん範囲のでかいやつだぞ
Use the longest range.
（ゼツ）分かってる
I know.
（干柿ほしがき鬼鮫きさめ）３日ですか
Three days?
大蛇丸おろちまるがいないぶん
Shouldn't we consider that it might
take a bit longer
もう少し時間を見たほうが
いいんじゃないですかね
since we don't have Orochimaru?
（暁リーダー）
そう思うなら さっさと始めよう
If that's what you think,
then get right to it.
That's true.
（うちはイタチ）そうだな
（鬼鮫）確かに
Indeed.
それがいい うん
That sounds good.
SPIRIT
BLUE
WHITE
RED
BOAR
SOUTH
NORTH
THREE
SPHERE
Sealing Jutsu: Nine Phantom Dragons.
（暁リーダー）
封印術･幻龍九封尽げんりゅうきゅうふうじん
Tsunade-sama.
綱手様
彼らが任務から帰ってきました
They have returned from their mission!
よし
All right.
（シズネ）あっ ちょっと綱手様
Oh, just a minute, Tsunade-sama.
お前たちにＳランク任務を与える
I'm giving you guys
an S-rank mission!
- Huh?
- No way.
（木こノ葉は丸まる）え？
（モエギ）ウソ…
ああ…
（木ノ葉丸）Ｓランク？
（モエギ）任務？
S-rank?
- Mission?
- Don't tell me...
（エビス）まさか…
（木ノ葉丸）
やった～！ Ｓランク任務だ
All right! We got an S-rank mission!
（モエギ）信じられない
I can't believe it...
ついに 俺たちの実力が
認められたんだな コレ
Our ability has finally
been acknowledged!
そっ そんなはず…
I-It can't be!
エビス先生 大丈夫？
Are you okay, Ebisu-sensei?
いや 昨日
少し温泉につかりすぎましてね
Well, I spent a bit too long soaking
in the hot spring, you see.
（ウドン）っていうより
のぞき してたんじゃあ…
More like you were peeping.
俺たち 忍者になって初めての
Ｓランク任務だってのに
Here this is the first S-rank mission
for us since we became Ninja.
かぜひいてんじゃねえよ コレ
Don't be catching a cold,
you closet pervert!
むっつりスケベ
なんだ？ こいつら
What's with these guys?
綱手様 違います
This is the wrong room, Tsunade-sama.
They're over here.
こっちです
ったく 紛らわしい
Geez, how confusing.
（３人）えっ？
（フスマを閉める音）
（木ノ葉丸）俺たちのＳランクは？
What about our S-rank mission?
勘違いですね
It was a misunderstanding...
Thank goodness.
よかった
お前たちにも
カカシ班と同様の任務をしてもらう
I'm giving you guys the same mission
as Team Kakashi.
砂へ向かい カカシたちと
サポートし合い任務をこなせ
Head for the Sand and
complete the mission
by providing backup for Kakashi
and the others.
分かったな
Got it?!
Yes, ma'am!
（マイト･ガイ）ははっ！
Please leave it to us.
（ロック･リー）任せてください
（テンテン）了解です
Roger.
（日向ひゅうがネジ）承知
Understood.
よし
All right!
ガイ班 これより出動します
Team Guy heading into action.
はっ は…
（綱手）かぜか？
（ガイ）いや…
You catch a cold?
No, my hay fever started
acting up before...
少し前から花粉症気味でして
ハハハ…
All right, we'll make it to
the Sand in one day.
よーし みんな
砂まで１日で行くぞ
ガイ先生 半日で行きましょう
Guy-sensei, let's make it in half a day.
どう考えたって３日はかかる
It'll take three days, no matter
how you consider it.
そういうノリでする会話
やめてください
Please stop your conversations
with that carried-away mood...
も～う
（ガイ）
あ～ 出発だ　みんな 俺に続け
All right, we're leaving!
Together with me, everyone.
The dash of youth!
青春ダッシュ！
（リー）はい ガイ先生
Yes, Guy-sensei!
（テンテン）もう 恥ずかしい
How embarrassing.
（ネジ）諦めろ テンテン
Give it up, Tenten.
相変わらず元気な連中だ
They're as energetic as ever.
アッハハ
It's sure been awhile
since we've seen Naruto.
ナルトに会うのも久しぶりだな
I'm looking forward to seeing
how much he's grown.
どれだけ成長してるか楽しみです
そうね
Yeah.
んっ もう少しで
砂隠れの里だっていうのに
Here we're so close to
the Village Hidden in the Sand...
I can't just sit around waiting!
もう待てねえってばよ
（カカシ）ナルト
焦っちゃダメって言ってるでしょ
Naruto, I told you not to
lose your patience.
でもよ
But...!
辛抱しなさい
Be patient. Right now, Temari-san is
the one who's the most anxious.
今 いちばん不安なのは
テマリさんなのよ
砂嵐に遭遇したら
その場でじっとしてるのが鉄則だ
The ironclad rule is to
stay put right there
if you encounter a sandstorm.
砂嵐の中では方向感覚が狂う
You lose your sense of direction
in a sandstorm.
砂漠をさまよったあげく
We often hear of people
脱水して死ぬというのは
よくある話だ
dying of dehydration after
getting lost in the desert.
大丈夫
It'll be okay.
この時期の砂嵐は
そう長く続かないはずだから
A sandstorm around this time
of year shouldn't last too long.
早くやんでくれ
Please let up soon.
カンクロウ
Kankuro...
鎮静剤を
Give him a sedative.
はい
Okay.
（医療忍者）
我々にできるのは もう
痛みを和らげることくらいです
All we can do now is ease his pain...
Our only ray of hope is the Leaf Shinobi
who are scheduled to arrive tomorrow.
いちるの望みは
あすにでも到着する予定の
木ノ葉の忍です
もし その中にも毒の専門家がいれば
If they have a poison specialist
with them...
無論 それまでカンクロウの体力も
持てばの話ですが
If Kankuro can hold on
that long, of course.
木ノ葉方面の道は
今 砂嵐で通行できなくなっている
The road from the Leaf is currently
impassable due to a sandstorm.
最悪 到着は
数日 遅れるかもしれん
In the worst case,
they could arrive several days late.
そうなれば もう絶望的です
If that happens,
then it's hopeless.
情けないの
This is pathetic...
よもや 木ノ葉の助けを
当てにする日がこようとは…
I can't believe the day has come when
we have to rely on the aid of the Leaf.
姉ちゃん 疲れたじゃろ
Aren't you tired, Nee-chan?
Let's have a seat outside.
あっちで座ろうか
昨日から一睡もしとらんじゃろ
You haven't had a wink of
sleep since yesterday, right?
（チヨ）
何が悲しゅうて 木ノ葉なんぞに…
It's so sad,
having to depend on the Leaf...
あ～あ
姉ちゃん
Nee-chan.
寝たか
She fell asleep, huh?
（砂の里の忍）早ければ
木ノ葉の助っ人すけっとが来るころだが…
If they're early, the help from the Leaf
should be arriving pretty soon.
（砂の里の忍）昨日の嵐ですから
But even a local wouldn't be
able to get here quickly
地元の者でさえ
そう早くは来られませんよ
with yesterday's sandstorm.
あっ おい あれは…
Hey, what's that?
（砂の里の忍たち）おおっ
Oh!
（砂の里の忍）お待ちしてました
We've been expecting you.
（砂の里の忍）
テマリさんもご一緒でしたか
So you were with them, Temari-san?
（砂の里の忍）さあ こちらです
Please, come this way.
何？ カンクロウまでやられたのか
What?! They got Kankuro, too?
はい 風影様が連れ去られてしまい
Yes, Kazekage-sama was taken and
Kankuro-dono followed in pursuit.
カンクロウ殿が そのあとを追って
しかも 敵の毒にやられてしまい
解毒方法も分からず
He was poisoned by the enemy
and we don't know how to neutralize it.
At this rate... he won't...
このままでは もう…
Damn it!
くそっ
（サクラ）
急ぎましょう テマリさん
Let's hurry, Temari-san.
私が診ます
I'll take a look at him.
"Treatment Room 3"
（テマリ）カンクロウ！
Kankuro!
カンクロウ！
（チヨ）あっ あヤツは…
He's... the White Fang of the Leaf!
木ノ葉の白い牙
おのれ！
You jerk!
（カカシ）んっ？
Huh?
Prepare yourself!
覚悟！
When I look up at the sky.
sora wo miagereba
♪～
The stars, see, are sparkling.
hoshitachi ga hora matataiteru
Each giving off its own light.
kono hoshi no hitotachi mitai ni
Like the people on this planet.
samazama na hikari wo hanatte
Yeah, so among them, I too,
sono naka de boku mo
want to shine particularly bright.
hitokiwa kagayaite itain da
I close my eyes and make a vow in my heart,
me wo tojite kokoro ni chikau
and entrust my dreams to that shooting star.
nagareboshi ni yume wo takushite
I'm in my usual park.
koko wa itsumo no kouen
I can see the night scenery on the slide.
yakei ga mieru suberidai no ue
That's been my special seat for years.
mukashi kara boku no tokutouseki
Whenever I'm worried about something, I come here.
nayami ga areba koko ni kurun desu
Just like then, I'm on my way to my dreams.
ano koro no mama yume no tochuu de
But unable to fulfil them.
ima de kanaerarezu ni irun desu
Maybe this is the end of the line.
moshikashite koko ga mou shuuten
There are days when I say weak things like that.
nante yowane wo haite shimaisou na hi mo aru
But every time, I remember.
demo sono tabi ni omoidasu
That starry sky where I looked for a shooting star.
nagareboshi wo sagashite ano hoshizora
The wish I made when I was little hasn't changed even now.
chiisana koro no negaigoto ima mukashi mo kawaranai mama
When I look up at the sky.
sora wo miagereba
The stars, see, are sparkling.
hoshitachi ga hora matataiteru
Each giving off its own light.
kono hoshi no hitotachi mitai ni
Like the people on this planet.
samazama na hikari wo hanatte
Yeah, so among them, I too,
sono naka de boku mo
want to shine particularly bright.
hitokiwa kagayaite itain da
I close my eyes and make a vow in my heart,
me wo tojite kokoro ni chikau
～♪
and entrust my dreams to that shooting star.
nagareboshi ni yume wo takushite
Next Episode
Medical Emergency 24 hours.
緊急医療24時
Today we're reporting live from
the Hidden Sand Medical Facility.
今回は 砂隠れの医療施設から
お送りしています
It appears that a new patient
has been brought in just now.
今 新たな患者が
運び込まれたようです
The patient is a 17-year-old Jonin,
poisoned, and in critical condition.
患者は17歳 上忍じょうにん
毒を受けて重体
Oh, his Kumadori make up
is being washed off!
あっ くま取りが
落とされていきます
The surgeon seems to be a girl.
ドクターは女性のようです
Can such a young doctor handle this?
こんな若いドクターで
大丈夫なんでしょうか
It looks like the toxin is
being sucked out... however!
どうやら
毒が吸い出されていきます が…
Despite their medical efforts,
今 必死の治療むなしく
お亡くなりになったもようです
it appears they have just
lost the patient.
Hey, don't kill me off just like that!
って勝手に殺すな！
Next time: "The Medical Ninja's Student"
The Medical Ninja's Student
次回
「医療忍者の弟子」
Notable People in the Leaf Village
Notable People in the Leaf Village.
このコーナーは 毎回
里の有名人をお招きして
In this feature, we invite
someone famous from the village
and ask them all sorts of questions.
いろいろ聞いちゃうコーナーです
Our guest today is the only woman
among the legendary Sannin.
きょうのゲストは
伝説の３人の紅一点
木ノ葉の五代目火影ほかげ 綱手様
Tsunade-sama,
the Fifth Hokage of the Leaf!
Ahem!
（サクラ）比類なき怪力と
医療忍術で里を見守る
She protects the village
with her unsurpassed strength
and medical Ninjutsu!
強く美しい最強のくノ一
She is the greatest
and most beautiful Kunoichi there is!
Master! Please tell us
the secret to your beautiful figure.
師匠 ナイスバディの秘密を
教えてください
To be straight, you need to
get an appropriate amount of sleep.
（綱手）ずばり
適度な睡眠を取ることだ
（サクラ）なるほど
I see.
（綱手）
プラス百薬の長たる酒の摂取
Plus intake of the best medicine
there is; alcohol!
This also has the effect of
attaining beautiful skin.
これは美肌にも効果がある
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
（サクラ）うんうん
And then of course, there's...
（綱手）あとは やはり…
（ナルト）ストップ！
Stop! This won't do, Sakura-chan!
ダメだってばよ サクラちゃん
ばあちゃんの体型なんか目指しちゃ
There's no point to wanting to
have the body of the Granny!
Huh?
（綱手）ああ？
（ナルト）あんなんなったら
With a body like that,
your breasts would get in the way
胸が邪魔して動きづらくて
and you wouldn't be able to move.
It's not worth it.
いいことねえってばよ
Sure enough,
the nimble and slender body
やっぱ サクラちゃんは
身軽でスレンダーな
今のままで十分…
you've got now is enough...
Excuse me for being nimble.
身軽で悪かったわね
Now you've said it.
言ってくれるね
Huh?
（ナルト）はい？
Divine punishment!
（サクラ･綱手）天誅てんちゅう！
（ナルト）
なはっ ぐっ…
T
o
b
e
c
o
n
t
i
n
u
e
d
.